

PROFILE

A 23 years old serious and reliable person with a various serior skills always trying to improve and renew. looking for opportunities in which he can apply, his skills and benevolent attitude

Programming: JavaScrpit, NodeJS, React, MySQL, PHP Python, git, VBA ...

Git : https://github.com/
GraineFutee

PERSONAL INFO

Date of birth: 16/10/1996 (23)

Nationality: French

Phone number : +33 784 543 925

Mail: pierre.asdrubal@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

French: proficient

English · proficient

Spanish: beginner

German: beginner

Swedish: in progress

PIERRE ASDRUBAL

EXPERIENCE

BARISTA/SERVIS, ICANDER'S; STOCKHOLM, SWEDEN — MAR 2020 - APR 2020 Preparing coffees, taking orders, serving drinks, cleaning tables.

STOCK MANAGER, OCP REPARTITION; BAULE, FRANCE — JUNE - AUGUST 2019 Managing stocks for a pharmaceutical company (high level standards), taking care of the quarantine area (out of date products, batch problems ...). Proceeding to the destruction/ negotiate with the supplier to get refunds. Developing automates

BARTENDER/WAITER, DOYLE'S ON THE BEACH; SYDNEY, AUSTRALIA — SEPT 2018 - FEB 2019

Preparing Drinks and coffees following dockets, advising on cocktails and wines, taking orders, serving drinks, setting and cleaning tables.

SALESMAN; SYDNEY, AUSTRALIA — AUGUST — SEPT 2018

Door to door sales, promoting a new mechanic in order to bring new loyal customers. Following courses in the morning and working in the afternoon.

WEB DEVELOPER, THALES LAS; FLEURY-LES-AUBRAIS, FRANCE — 2016 - 2018

Supply chain manager assistant and web developer; Planning & managing projects on my own or in team. Multiple automate in order to help people save time & gain in standardisation. The main project was the study and the build of a new ERP making easier the future transfer to SAP (Web application -> PHP). We were a team of 3 developer following an AGILE process.

EDUCATION

University of Orleans, France - IT Diploma 2017

University of Orleans, France - Industrial Logistics Diploma 2016